♪ My country 'tis of thee... ♪
♪ ...liberty ♪
♪ It's really great. ♪
(Leonard:)So, when Howard said the FBI
would be contacting me,
(Leonard:)I was expecting Mulder.
(Leonard:)Glad to see I got Scully.
(Page:)Who?
(Leonard:)Mulder and Scully.
X-Files.
"The truth is out there."
(Leonard:)Never mind.
(Leonard:)Uh, so, what would you
like to know?
(Page:)You work with Mr. Wolowitz here
at the university, correct?
(Leonard:)Yes. Of course, we're in
different departments.
(Leonard:)He's an engineer and I'm
an experimental physicist.
(Leonard:)You know, one
of those guys
(Leonard:)who examines the building blocks
of creation
(Leonard:)and says,
"Hello, maker of the universe.
"I see what you did there.
Good one."
(Woman at Door:)Right.
(Page:)Now, how would you characterize
(Page:)your relationship
with Mr. Wolowitz?
(Howard:)Good.
(Leonard:)It's a good
relationship.
(Leonard:)Of course, most of my
relationships are good.